>> Brian Holt: 让我们进行错误边界。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's go do error boundary.
因此，请重命名 ErrorBoundary.tsx。
So rename ErrorBoundary.tsx.
>> Brian Holt: 希望你在这里侦测到我刚重命名的模式
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And hopefully you're
sensing a pattern here that I just renamed
文件我把问题解决了
the file, and I just fixed the problems.
这就是这里的过程。
And that's just kind of the process here.
我帮助将一个位于 LinkedIn 的代码库迁移到 typescript 中，并且
I helped to migrate one a the code bases
at LinkedIn to be in typescript, and
这就是我一个月来做的
that's literally what I did for a month.
这就是重命名文件并解决问题。
That's just rename files and fix it.
问别人你在做什么
And ask people,
what the hell were you doing?
还是想
Or thinking?
那是我一般的工作
That's kind of my job in general.
所以我要把这个从一个有构造的人
So, I'm gonna move this from
being on a constructor to being
公共类属性。
a public class property.
你也完全可以这样做你可以通过
Again you totally could just do it like
this, and you could pass in what the state
是，但是我喜欢把它做得更好。
is, but I like doing it as
public class properties better.
所以我要删除这个，并将它移到构造函数之外，
So I'm just going to delete that, and
move that outside of the constructor, and
删除构造函数。
delete the constructor.
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们会说这是一个公共状态。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then we're
gonna say this is a public state.
我们会说这是一个公共的静态
We're gonna say this is a public static,
公共，公共和公共。
public, public and public.
>> Brian Holt: 我们必须告诉它错误的确是错误，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We have to tell it
that errors are indeed errors,
信息为 ErrorInfo。
and the info is ErrorInfo.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And that's it.
所有其他事物都能找到它是什么
Everything else it can
figure out what it is.
> > Brian Holt: Great ，任何问题?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Great, any questions?
这很容易
That was pretty easy.
>> Brian Holt: 我认为这也是你会发现的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I think that's
what you'll find as well.
所以，这就是我告诉人们想要搬上打字本的东西。
So, this is what I tell people
that wanna move to typescript.
我有个很棒的推文我晚点给你看
I actually have a really great
tweet that I'll show you later,
把 typescript 迁移到痛苦的过程中你只是在质疑
that migrating the typescript is so
painful, and you're just questioning,
我为什么要这样折磨自己
why did I subject myself to this torture?
直到你把你密码的 60% 用在打字员上
Until you get to about 60% of your
code's base being in typescript,
突然之间一切都很神奇
and then all of a sudden,
everything is magical.
突然之间，这想法很棒，你是个天才。
All of a sudden, this was a fantastic
idea and you're a genius.
这就是我的生活的故事
[LAUGH] That's kind of
the story of my life.
我只是有点像个白痴一样上下
I just kinda go up and
down like I'm an idiot.
然后我是个天才但大部分是白痴公园
And then I'm a genius,
but mostly the idiot park.
总之这不是和布莱恩的治疗
Anyway, this is not therapy with Brian.
但我想说的是你会想知道
What I wanna say though, is there's gonna
be parts of this where you're gonna wonder
我为什么选择这样对自己
why did I choose to do this to myself?
付款人真的来了，你的代码大部分都是用打字员来的
And the payoff really comes once, most of
your code bases in typescript because then
我想你的代码库会开始聚结
your code base will start kind of
coalescing into like coherence, I suppose.
而且很高兴你能从另一个团队里输入一个文件
And, it'll be nice like you can just
import a file from another team, and
你可以看到它的所有类型和旧的类型的检查
you can see all the types in it,
and old type check all that stuff.
这都是有道理的。
It all makes sense.
好吧
So, yeah.
这就是我要说的，耐心一点。
That's what I would say,
just be patient a little bit.
库兹你必须要经过很多时间才开始有任何意义
Cuz you have to get through a lot of
it before it starts making any sense.